# **JASON NELSON**

## jasonnelson11@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jason-n-84778a124/ https://github.com/jasondamion https://jasondesigns.net

### **Summary**

Full stack web developer continuously learning the new tech being applied in the technology field today. Experienced with excellent client and project management skills. Dedicated to building customer loyalty and promoting win-win results for the company and the client. Action-oriented with strong ability to communicate effectively with technology, executive, and business audiences.

## **Technology**

**Certifications:** AWS Cloud Practitioner

Front-End: HTML5, BootStrap, CSS3, JQuery, Ajax, DOM Manipulation, Handlebars, Javascript, API's, React.JS

Back-End: Node.JS, Express.JS, MySQL, Java, MongoDB, Sequelize/Mongoose

Software: Github, Git Version Control, Firebase, Git Bash, Command Prompt, FTP Client, AWS Console/CLI/SDK

## **Projects**

## Daycare Manager | Node.js, MySQL | Github

**Full Stack Developer** 

Single-page web app for managing my church daycare.

- Incorporates Express.Js to host a local server to render the code on the laptop..
- Dynamically renders features and components using Handlebar.js with Sequelize.
- Utilizes Bootstrap, CSS, and SQL gueries to retrieve the children and their timesheets.

## Student Mingle | API's | Algorithms | Github | Live

**Full Stack Developer** 

A web app designed to meet students with similar interests as the user.

- Interests are gathered via a survey.
- Point-based algorithm decides who is the closest match to you.
- Modal shows your match along with a picture.

# **Heavenly Joy Events** | Nodemailer | Cloudinary | <u>Github</u> | <u>Live</u>

**Full Stack Developer** 

A Kids Venue web app for reserving parties.

- Able to build your own party and customize it.
- Gallery available to give you a feel for the party.
- Contact Page available for guestions.'

## **Professional Experience**

Etomon New York,NY 2019-Current

#### **Back-End Developer Intern**

- Work with developers to implement back-end services, APIs, and internal tools.
- Debug issues and address performance bottlenecks.
- Integrate applications with databases and work with table structures and data querying.
- Implement unit tests.
- Read and produce technical documentation.

Domino's Pizza Dumont, NJ 2019-Current

#### ASSISTANT MANAGER

- Coordinate daily customer service operations (e.g. sales processes, orders and payments)
- Monitor and maintain store inventory
- Handle complaints from customers
- Evaluate employee performance and identify hiring and training needs
- Supervise and motivate staff to perform their best

### **Customer Service Representative**

- Responsible for daily operational duties
- Training of new staff and managers
- Direct management of inbound call and order taking
- In charge of customer grievance resolution
- Directed shift peak times during management absence
- Responsible for pizza preparation

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

2018-2019

Rutgers University, Jersey City, NJ, United States

Bachelors in Computer Science 2019-Current

University of The People, Online University, CA, United States